Subindex build by Linnet
http://linnet.126.com  http://blog.csdn.net/redbirdli
火鸟字幕合并器SubindexV0.5
Created time 11.10.31 10:53:08
-=The Last Fantasy=-
Hold nothing back! Leave it all on the floor!
-How much time we got? -We've got fifteen minutes tops!
Just enough time to get in and out!
All right, let's do this thing!
Are you ready now, Clark?
Yeah. I forgot to press the record button. Sorry.
So, Mr. Luthor...
...any more secret construction projects at LuthorCorp like Level 3?
Please, call me Lex.
-Lex, are you gonna answer my question? -Chloe.
-What? -It's okay, Clark.
"Our critics are our friends. They show us our faults."
Benjamin Franklin.
Excuse me, Mr. Luthor...
-...your father's on the phone. -I need to get this.
I'll take it in the conservatory.
I look forward to resuming our verbal judo.
-All right, boys, this is the big one! -Yeah! Let's do it!
Let's go!
I wonder if he's really taking a call or if he's just trying to avoid me?
Wow, that's really cool.
Do you think it's real?
Chloe?
Chloe.
Okay. The vault's in the wall behind the bookcase.
-How do you know? -I've got my sources.
-He was doing one of the housekeepers. -Oh, yeah.
-We got five minutes, let's move it! -Let's do it!
That's it, boys, come on. It's payday!
One minute!
-Come on, let's go! -I only got one arm.
Yeah!
Time's up! Let's move it! Let's go!
You can't just go snooping around someone's house.
Clark, it's a mansion. It's designed for snooping.
Okay, fine. We'll go and wait in the library...
...for Lex to officially blow us off.
-I'll put the camera away. -Okay, I'm gonna go get my bag.
Hey, what's going on?
Chloe, run!
Move it! Let's move it!
Clark!
Chloe.
Chloe!
翻译:龙猫，versus，点点姑娘，颀觎 校对:岁月倒影，TYY
别犹豫！动手要干净利落！
- 我们有多少时间？ - 最多十五分钟！
刚好够来回一趟！
好，我们干吧！
这回准备好了吧，克拉克？
是，我刚才忘了按记录键 不好意思
那么，卢瑟先生…
…卢瑟公司还有更多像第三层那样 秘密建设的项目吗？
拜托，叫我莱克斯
- 莱克斯，你会回答我的问题吗？ - 克罗伊
- 什么？ - 没事，克拉克
“…批评者是我们的朋友 他们指出我们的错误”
本杰明・富兰克林的名言吧
打扰了，卢瑟先生…
- …您父亲来电 - 我得接这电话
我到花房去接电话
我期待继续与你唇枪舌战
- 好的，兄弟们，这是笔大买卖！ - 是啊！我们干吧！
走吧！
我怀疑他是真的在接电话 还是要躲我？
哇，这个真酷
你认为它是真品吗？
克罗伊？
克罗伊
好的，金库在墙里面，书架后面
- 你怎么知道？ - 我自有消息来源
- 他勾搭过这的一个佣人 - 哦，爽啊
- 我们有五分钟，赶紧动手吧！ - 我们干吧！
就是这些，兄弟们，今天发财了！
剩一分钟了！
- 快啊，走了！ - 我只有一只手
时间到了！走啊！快走！
你不能在人家房子里到处窥探
克拉克，这么大的宅邸 当然就是用来被窥探的
好吧，行 我们去书房等吧…
…等着莱克斯正式宣布放我们鸽子
- 我把相机收了 - 好，我要去拿我的包
嘿，这是怎么回事？
克罗伊，快跑啊！
跑啊！快跑啊！
克拉克！
克罗伊
克罗伊！
片名:超人前传
主题曲《Save me》:谁来拯救我
领衔主演：汤姆・威灵
让你温暖的手伸出驱散我的痛苦
主演:克丽斯汀・克鲁克
谁来拯救我
主演:迈克尔・罗森巴姆
我不在乎你是怎么做到
主演：埃里克・约翰森
只要你留下，和我在一起
主演：山姆・琼斯三世
快来吧，我一直在等待着你
主演：艾利森・麦克
主演：安妮特・奥图尔
第十三集:动力
约翰・施耐得 饰演 强纳森・肯特
我一直留着整个世界只为你闪耀
超人始创作者:杰瑞・希杰尔和乔・夏斯特
留下，留下
快出现吧
电视策划:阿尔弗雷德・哥夫，麦尔斯・米莱
客串主演:大卫・拉夫格伦
卡万・史密斯
克拉克
Clark.
大卫・科尔斯
Don't worry, I brought in the best doctors from Metropolis.
别担心，我从大都会找了最好的医生
- 她会好起来吗？ - 医生也不确定
-Is she gonna be all right? -Doctors aren't sure.
摔得挺严重，她左手摔断了 而且脑震荡了
The fall was pretty bad. She broke her left arm and has a concussion.
莎拉-简・雷蒙德
他们需要确定没有脑肿胀
They wanna make sure there's no brain swelling.
我本该抓住她
I should've gotten to her.
我不是有意要嗦几句 克拉克，可这不是你的错
I don't mean to belabor the obvious, Clark, but this isn't your fault.
我就是想不通这到底怎么回事 房间本来是空的…
I just don't know what happened. One minute, the room is empty...
联合执行制片:格列哥・比曼
…可一瞬间他们就凭空出现了
...and then they appear out of thin air.
警察有什么线索吗？
I mean, do the police have any leads?
他们认为我不是第一个受害者
They don't think I'm the first one that's been hit.
县里共发生超过十二起劫案
There have been over a dozen robberies all over the county.
监督制片:马克・伏黑顿
这伙人不知怎么做到的 无声无息就能进屋，锁头都不用撬
他们甚至想袭击斯摩维尔储贷银行
They tried to hit the Smallville Savings & Loan.
我从没听说过
I didn't hear about that.
银行不会公布未遂的劫案 那样会损害它们的形象
Banks don't publicize attempted robberies, it's bad for their image.
联合制片:迈克尔・格林
If nothing was taken, how do they know they were robbed?
如果没有东西被拿走 他们怎么能知道差点被劫了？
显然是他们触响了金库里的警报
Apparently they tripped an alarm inside the vault.
尽管这样，也没人知道他们是怎么进去的
Although, no one knows how they got in there.
警察能追踪到任何他们从你那偷走的东西吗？
And the stuff they stole from you. Can the police trace it?
我没有上报任何东西被盗，克拉克
I didn't report anything stolen, Clark.
联合制片:道里斯・伊根
-Why not? I saw them walk out with bags. -I don't care about that.
- 为什么不？我看见他们拿着包走了 - 我不在乎
联合制片:格雷格・沃克
I just want to find the people who did this to Chloe. When I do...
我只是想找出对克罗伊行凶的人 当我找到他们时…
制片:鲍勃・哈格罗夫
...I promise you, they will be dealt with accordingly.
…我向你保证，他们会受到应有的惩罚
- 什么意思？ - 就是说，这事你让我来管就行了
-What does that mean? -It means you should let me worry about it.
联合执行制片:肯・霍顿
你还不回家休息下吗？
Now, why don't you go home and get some rest?
本集编剧:菲利普・利文斯
导演:罗伯特・辛格
惠特尼
Whitney.
嘿，惠特尼，等一下
Hey, Whitney, wait up.
- 我以为你会在医院和我见面呢 - 对不起，我忘了，克罗伊怎么样了？
-Thought you're meeting me at the hospital. -I'm sorry, I forgot. How's Chloe?
好点了，但是还没过危险期
Better, but not out of the woods yet.
这就是镇上的事 总会有办法让你压抑
That's the thing with this town. It'll always find a way to keep you down.
惠特尼，怎么了，是因为你爸爸的事吗？
Whitney, what's wrong? Is it your dad?
不，没事，我要去整理存货了
No, it's nothing. I've just got to go do inventory.
回见
See you.
嗨，克拉克，你在干什么？
Hi, Clark. What are you doing?
- 让自己干点有用的事呗 - 嘿，儿子…
-Trying to make myself useful. -Hey, son...
…我们需要柴火，不是牙签
...we need firewood, not toothpicks.
我知道你们要说什么:这不是我的错
I know what you guys are gonna say: It's not my fault.
- 这话莱克斯和克罗伊老爸已经说过了 - 他们是对的，克拉克，你尽力了
-Lex already told me, so did Chloe's dad. -They're right, Clark. You did your best.
- 克罗伊当时说不定会没命了 - 儿子…
-Chloe could've died. -Son...
…成熟的人要学会去懂深刻的道理…
...becoming an adult means learning difficult lessons...
…其中一点就是你救不了每个人，不管你是谁
...one of which is you can't save everybody, no matter who you are.
你说你当时感觉到有陨石在附近
You said you felt the effects of the meteor rocks.
对，我只是不知道从哪来的
Yeah, I just don't know where it was coming from.
有时我真希望可以离开这个小镇 离陨石远远的
Sometimes I just wish I could leave this town and get away from the meteor rocks.
我肯定你可以，想走一定有机会的
I'm sure that you will. You'll get that chance.
但是逃避不能真正解决问题
But running away won't solve anything.
想要让自己变得更有用 就别耽在这里，只为自己伤情了
Don't hang around here feeling sorry for yourself.
行动吧，看看你能查出什么
Go. See what you can find out.
我不知道我在这存放了这么多东西
I had no idea I stored so much stuff in here.
- 你把那个胶带递给我吗，拜托了？ - 好
-Will you hand me the tape, please? -Yeah.
我还是不敢相信 你就要卖了这个地方，妮尔
I still can't believe you're selling this place, Nell.
我无法相信你怎么 突然就对这地方产生兴趣的
I can't believe your sudden interest in the place.
我父母从前在这里相遇 这地方对我意义重大
My parents met here. This place means a lot to me.
我知道，拉娜…
I know, Lana...
…但小电影院无法与大影院抗衡的 而且根本原因是…
...but one screen can't compete with a multiplex. And the fact is...
…我卖它是为了有足够的学费 能送你去读任何你想去的大学
...I wanna be able to send you to any college you want.
你能告诉我买家是谁吗？
Could you tell me who the buyer is?
或许我可以跟他们谈谈 看看他们愿不愿意把这里修复了
Maybe I could talk to them. See if they'd be willing to renovate.
是莱克斯・卢瑟
It's Lex Luthor.
斯摩维尔镇 储蓄与贷款银行
Lex said the people who hit the mansion tried to rob this bank.
莱克斯说袭击公馆的人想抢这家银行
我送你几个词：给官方警察调查
I've got three words for you: official police investigation.
那些警察什么都没干成呢
The police haven't done a thing.
过去六个月已经有12起抢劫案了 都用那种奇怪的作案方式
There have been 12 robberies in the past six months with the same freaky m.o.
没有任何人进门的迹象，珠宝和现金就不见了
No sign of entry, the jewels and the cash just vanished.
只有这个地方幸免，莱克斯说 他们触动了金库里面的一个警报器
Except for this place. Lex says that they triggered an alarm inside the vault.
- 问题是，他们怎么进去的？ - 我想不到
-The question is, how'd they get inside? -I don't know.
现在，别再专想克罗伊的事了，快走吧
Now, stop channeling Chloe and come on.
哦，不，不会又使肯特的千里眼吧
Oh, no, not the Kent thousand-yard stare.
克拉克！走吧，老兄
Clark! Come on, man.
我知道你感觉很糟，我也是
I know you feel bad. I do too.
但我们不是警察
But we're not cops.
什么消息都没有,那达
Nothing. Nada.
连个后续报道都没有 被盗十万现金珠宝，人肯定会报警的啊
Not a single sidebar. A guy has got to miss a hundred grand in cash and jewels.
卢瑟就不会报警，兄弟
Not Luthor, bro.
没人知道他在那个城堡里藏了多少钱
There is no telling how much jack he's got stashed in that castle.
现金，珠宝，艺术品，汽车，应有尽有！
Cash, jewels, art, cars, you name it!
如果我们下楼，没准还发现他在钱坑里游泳…
If we went downstairs, we would've found the money pit where he swims in the stuff...
- …就像那个有爱尔兰口音的鸭子 - 你说的是抠门的史高治（唐老鸭的舅舅）
-...like that duck with the Irish accent. -Uncle Scrooge.
- 是啊，是 - 他是苏格兰口音，不是爱尔兰
-Yeah, yeah. -He was Scottish, not Irish.
就算他有钱让我们抢，时间也不够了 我们那种能力不能像原来一样持久了
We don't have enough time. This stuff doesn't last as long as it used to.
我知道，我知道
I know, I know.
我告诉你，我们需要新人加入
I'm telling you, we need fresh blood.
- 是啊，但是我们该相信谁呢？ - 我不知道
-Yeah, but who can we trust? -I don't know.
我想我知道卢瑟为什么没上报劫案了
I think I know why Luthor didn't file that robbery report.
看下这个
Check this out.
这生发水广告男孩不想让人知道他进了…
The poster boy for Rogaine doesn't want anyone to know he's tapped into...
…他老爸的电脑系统
...his daddy's computer system.
我们可以再去拜访小卢瑟敲一笔了，哈？
Maybe then we pay Luthor Junior another visit, huh?
我想也是
I think so.
我不管
I don't care.
如果我想听借口，找警察就行了
If I wanted excuses, I'd call the police.
啊？好吧，你们哪还算是大都会 最好的私人保安公司
Yeah? Well, you're supposed to be the best private security firm in Metropolis.
你们怎么进来的？
How'd you get in here?
和上次一样的方法呗，兄弟
The same way we did last time, bro.
- 我要叫警察了 - 你上次没叫，我们知道为什么
-I'm calling the police. -You didn't last time, and we know why.
我们看了那张磁碟，莱克斯
We read the disk, Lex.
- 我不知道你在说什么 - 你在从你爸那里搜刮钱…
-What are you talking about? -You're skimming money from your dad...
…去资助斯摩维尔的一个项目
...to fund a project in Smallville.
那关系到一个甲烷发酵工厂 它将使我们的竞争对手倒闭
That concerns a methane treatment plant. It'll put our competitors out of business.
甲烷工厂不需要粒子加速器吧
Methane plants don't need particle accelerators.
- 你们想要什么？ - 一百万，现金
-What do you want? -A million, cash.
如果你想做什么反抗的蠢事，甚至只想试试…
If you try anything stupid, even if you think a stupid thought...
…你那张磁碟就会被上传到网上…
...your disk is going to be uploaded to the Internet...
…让全世界的人和莱诺大人都看见
...for all the world and Big Daddy Lionel to see.
我怎么和你们联系？
How do I reach you?
你不需要，我们会联系你
You don't. We reach you.
现在，转过去
Now, turn around.
等着
Wait there.
你们还不知道自己在和谁打交道
You have no idea who you're dealing with.
嘿，惠特尼
Hey, Whitney.
惠特尼？
Whitney?
- 嘿 - 我来给我妈取微波炉
-Hey. -I'm picking up a microwave for my mom.
去后面的柜台上拿吧
You can pick it up at the back counter.
一切都好吗？
Is everything okay?
我打赌你很愿意一辈子都呆在斯摩维尔
I bet you think it's just great to live in Smallville your whole life.
- 从爸爸那里接管农场 - 我不太想过那种生活
-Take over the farm from dad. -I'm not sure that's the life for me.
- 有时你没有选择 - 惠特尼，你能摆脱这里的
-Sometimes you don't have a choice. -Whitney, you'll get out of here.
- 你能比其他人走得更远的 - 我失去了奖学金，肯特
-You'll go further than anyone in town. -I lost my scholarship, Kent.
很遗憾
I'm sorry.
你告诉拉娜了吗？
Have you told Lana yet?
我将在这家店里度过我的余生…
I am going to spend the rest of my life in this store...
…像我爸一样在五十岁时得严重心脏病 然后死后成了“没人在意的那谁”就完了？
...develop a bad heart at fifty like my dad, and become just another "remember him?"
我永远都走不出斯摩维尔的
I'm never getting out of Smallville.
嘿，伙计，你这双鞋有十二号的吗？
Hey, man, you got these sneaks in a twelve?
有
Yeah.
有问题吗，老兄？
You got a problem, bro?
没
No.
我自己去找吧
I'll go find this.
嘿…
Hey...
- …你不就是惠特尼・佛得曼吗？ - 是
-...aren't you Whitney Fordman? -Yeah.
我是韦德・马哈尼
Wade Mahaney.
去年我看了你对抗托皮卡的比赛 扔出了300码，比赛很漂亮
I saw you throw 300 yards against Topeka last year. That was a great game.
我听说你因为这个 得到堪萨斯州立大学的全额奖学金
I heard you were tracked for a full ride to Kansas State.
- 奖金的事没成真，要十二号，对吗？ - 是，谢谢，伙计
-It didn't work out. Size twelve, right? -Yeah. Thanks, buddy.
兄弟，我很理解你
Man. Well, I know all about that.
11年级时，我就被球队解雇了 膝盖断裂，做了四个手术
Senior year I got sacked, blew out my knee, had to have four operations.
巨大的打击
Tough break.
原本有一打的学校要给我全额奖学金…
I had a dozen schools offer me full scholarships...
…然后一眨眼，全都没了
...and then it all went away, just like that.
那么，现在你有什么打算吗？
So, what's your plan now?
没有，就是不想后半辈子都做这个
Don't have one. Just don't want to do this the rest of my life.
我理解你，这能有什么未来呢 呃？怎么说…
I hear you. Where's the future in that, huh? Say...
…今晚我们那有一个派对
...we're having a party at our place tonight.
干嘛不来坐坐
Why don't you swing by.
不行，我得呆到店关门
I can't, I've got to close up.
关门后来吧，喝杯酒，当散闷
Come by after. Knock back a brew. Detox from this.
来啊，兄弟，会很好玩的
Come on, man, it'll be fun.
很好玩啊！
Fun!
我是四分卫的老大
I am the god of quarters.
我带你去四处看看，兄弟，走了
Let me give you the tour, bro. Come on.
- 这地方太棒了 - 也许我们能带上你，佛得曼
-This place is awesome. -Maybe we could bring you on, Fordman.
- 我们肯定需要你这么有天份的人 - 你们为什么要帮我？
-Always use a talented guy. -Why do you wanna help me?
我们这种人会相互吸引
Guys like us got to stick together.
在橄榄球生涯失败后 我以为这辈子就完了
I thought my life was over after football didn't pan out.
但那只是另一种开始
It was just beginning.
相信我…
Trust me...
…只会越来越好，我带你看看真正精彩的
...it only gets better. Let me show you where the real party is.
你纹身过没？
You ever been inked?
我对纹身没啥兴趣
I'm not really into tattoos.
是入伙仪式，兄弟 第一次免费
Initiation, bro. First one's on the house.
还是算了吧，好像永远洗不掉
I don't know, man, they're kind of forever.
- 你想成为大人物？ - 那就要像大人物一样
-You wanna eat with the big dogs? -You got to step up to the bowl.
你绝对从没见过这玩意
This is like nothing you've ever seen before.
我发誓，会让你觉得有如重生一般
Make you feel like a new man, swear to God.
坐吧
Have a seat.
好的
All right.
别纹个“斯摩维尔”上去就行了
Just make sure it doesn't say "Smallville."
哈哈，宝贝
Yeah, baby!
不要！不要！
No! No!
- 嘿，拜托 - 人车合一
-Hey! Hey, come on! -Be the truck!
- 人车合一！人车合一！ - 你们疯了吧！
-Be the truck! Be the truck! -You guys are crazy!
不要！
No!
- 哈哈！ - 哈哈！
-Yeah! -Yeah!
- 酷吧，宝贝！ - 酷吧！
-Yeah, baby! -Yeah!
- 看啊 - 看啊，你成功了！
-Yeah. -Yeah! You got it!
嘿
Hey.
你父亲打电话来说你醒了
Your dad called and told me you were awake.
恩，你确实是醒后第一位来看我的
You're officially my first visitor.
感觉怎样？
How you feeling?
就像被丢到洗衣机里面搅得完全虚脱一样
Like a million bucks, thrown in the washing machine and set on spin.
- 大家都很担心你 - 看出来了
-Everyone was real worried about you. -Yeah, I noticed.
看起来好像妮尔的花店被洗劫了
Looks like Nell's flower shop's been stripped clean.
我还真喜欢莱克斯送的这束
I especially like the ones from Lex.
让我感觉赢了肯塔基赛马大会一样
They make me feel like I won the Kentucky Derby.
好美，这才是我最喜欢的
They're beautiful, Clark. They're my favorite.
我…
I....
我只想说很抱歉
I just wanna say I'm sorry.
为什么？
For what?
让你受伤了
Letting you get hurt.
我应该很恼你是不是，克拉克
Well, I am perturbed with you, Clark.
谁让你连1871年的芝加哥大火都没扑灭呢
I'm also mad that you didn't put out the Chicago Fire of 1871.
你也没有阻止罗马帝国的衰亡 你也要为黑暗时代负直接责任是不？
Or prevent the fall of the Roman Empire, making you responsible for the Dark Ages.
谢谢
Thanks.
你记得当时那些人的情形么？
Do you remember anything about those guys?
记得一件事，抓住我的人前臂上有纹身
There was one thing. The guy that grabbed me had a tattoo on his forearm.
大概是个八角形吧
An octagon, maybe.
- 怎么了，克拉克？ - 我不知道
-What's going on, Clark? -I don't know.
让我去调查下
Let me do some digging.
克拉克・肯特要做调查报导者吗 听着还挺像回事啊
Clark Kent, investigative reporter. Has a nice ring to it.
- 休息吧 - 我尽量
-You get some rest. -I'll try.
谢谢你
Thank you.
这个剧场对很多人来说意义重大
This theater means something to a lot of people.
我童年时代的每个周六都在这里 就坐在第八排中间
I spent every Saturday of my childhood here, eighth row center.
每一次灯暗下来，屏幕闪烁起来…
When the lights went down and the screen flickered on...
门外的一切烦恼都消失不见了
...the problems outside these doors just disappeared.
像是被送到了一个神奇的地方
It was like being transported to a magical place.
故事很好，可到底为何对你如此重要？
That's a nice story, but why is it so important to you really?
我的父亲母亲在这里相遇 我想我需要一些可以留住的东西
My parents met here. I guess I'm just looking for something to hold on to.
我该只为拉娜同学的伤感回忆保留这里吗
I'm supposed to preserve this monument to Lana Lang's sentimental memories.
我不是这个意思
That's not what I meant.
你还是个孩子，拉娜 别老这么突如其来情感涌动的
You're a teenager, Lana. Mercurial doesn't do you justice.
我以为你会懂，看来我错了
Thought you might understand. Clearly I was mistaken.
这是生意，拉娜
This is business, Lana.
这里所有的商店都会变成办公场所 镇上也会需要一个停车场的
All these stores are becoming office spaces. This town needs a parking garage.
所以你要执行你的计划了
So you're going ahead with your plans.
你这种理由没法改变我的决定
You haven't given me any reason to change my mind.
不好意思，我还有别的要紧事要办
Now, if you'll excuse me, I have a pressing matter to attend to.
惠特尼，有时间吗？
Whitney, you have a minute?
有点忙
I'm kind of busy.
记得昨天来找鞋那家伙吗？
Remember the guy who came in yesterday, looking for shoes?
- 不记得，光顾的人太多了 - 没跟你开玩笑，惠特尼
-No. A lot of guys come in here. -Whitney, this is serious.
你轻点
Take it easy.
- 你在哪儿纹的身？ - 别多管闲事
-Where'd you get that tattoo? -Mind your own business.
是那些人给你纹的么？
Look, did those guys give it to you?
惠特尼，他们不是好人
Whitney, they're bad news.
你不是一直想抢走我的拉娜吗 现在怎么反倒帮起我来了？
You spend your time trying to steal Lana. Now, you wanna become my Boy Scout.
不是这样的
That's not true.
很难像别人看你这样看待你自己吧，肯特？
It's tough seeing yourself the way others see you, isn't it, Kent?
- 离那些人远点 - 你又不是我父亲，肯特
-Stay away from those guys. -You're not my father, Kent.
现在就给我滚
Now, get the hell out of here.
妮尔说你打电话过来，好像很紧急
Hey. Nell said you called. Sounded urgent.
- 今天看到惠特尼了吗？ - 有，我问他昨天干嘛去了
-Have you seen Whitney today? -Yeah. I asked him what was going on.
他说他跟新朋友出去玩，放松一下
He said he was out with some new friends, blowing off steam.
我想劝他，他却生气了，我也没办法
When I tried to press him, he got angry, so I backed off.
看着爱人受煎熬，自己又无能为力 这种感觉真是痛苦
It's hard watching people you love suffer and there's nothing you can do to help.
拉娜，我不知道该不该跟你说 不过惠特尼没有奖学金了
Lana, I don't know if I'm supposed to tell you this, but Whitney lost his scholarship.
什么？
What?
他怎么没跟我说？
Why didn't he tell me?
梦想离他如此之近，又一瞬间被夺走
He was so close to his dream, and then to just have it taken away like that.
他肯定万分痛苦
Must hurt like hell.
谢谢你告诉我
Thanks for telling me.
你是个好朋友
You're a good friend.
我查了下火炬报，这些是惠特尼的新朋友
I raided the Torch. I think these are Whitney's new friends.
96级的韦德・马哈尼和斯科特・鲍曼
Wade Mahaney and Scott Bowman. Class of '96.
六年前，他们跟惠特尼一样
-Who are these guys? -They were Whitney, six years ago.
明星级运动员，在各种比赛中为学校得奖 他们简直可以统治学校
Athletes, lettered in football, baseball, basketball. They ruled the school.
- 然后呢？ - 根据年鉴
-What happened? -Well, according to the Ledger...
韦德受伤了，斯科特开始吸毒
...Wade got injured and Scott started using drugs.
他们眼看着自己的未来堕落掉
They watched their futures vanish.
- 你觉得惠特尼有麻烦了？ - 我也不知道
-Do you think Whitney's in trouble? -I don't know.
我想跟他谈谈，但他根本不理我
I tried to talk to him, but he wouldn't listen to me.
他觉得奖学金是离开小镇的唯一途径
He thinks that scholarship is his only way out of here.
我希望他能像我看他那样看待他自己 有太多东西比橄榄球重要
I wish he'd see himself the way I do. There's more to him than football.
- 他很幸运有你 - 是啊
-He's lucky to have you. -Yeah.
就是对他没什么影响力
Big influence I am.
看来今天我就是不能说服任何人
Can't seem to convince anybody to do anything today.
你是说塔龙剧院？
Are you talking about the Talon?
我和莱克斯见面了，本来想说服他 结果却被他打垮了
I met with Lex, tried to make my case, but he totally shot me down.
他说我没能给他一个够好的商业理由
He said I hadn't given him a good enough business reason.
听起来很苛刻啊
Sounds kind of harsh.
是的
Yeah.
其实最让我抓狂的是他说的没错
But I think the thing that makes me maddest, is that he's right.
或许他这不是拒绝，而是一个挑战
Maybe it wasn't a rejection, maybe it was a challenge.
- 我首要的挑战是帮助惠特尼 - 那个让我来吧
-My first challenge is helping Whitney. -Let me work on that.
克拉克，我很感激你 可你为什么要做这些？
Clark, why are you doing this? Not that I don't appreciate it.
克罗伊的事，我没能阻止 这是救惠特尼的机会
I couldn't stop what happened to Chloe. There's a chance for Whitney.
你尝到甜头了吧？
You got a taste.
兄弟，还想见识全部的奥妙吗？
You wanna find out what it's all about, bro?
是的，当然，我加入
Yeah. Sure, I'm in.
很高兴你准点到了，莱克斯
Glad you could make it, Luthor.
进去，顺着走道，进一个后补式冷藏柜
Go inside. You'll find a walk-in meat locker.
在那里等着
Wait there.
接下来怎么办
Now what?
喂？
Hello?
- 你们为什么能…？ - 打开箱子，莱克斯
-How did you...? -Open the case, Lex.
- 先给我磁盘 - 先给钱，莱克斯
-I want the disk first. -The money, Lex.
先把钱给我们!
Give us the money!
- 发生什么事情了？ - 闭嘴
-What's going on? -Shut up.
箱子是空的，他玩我们！
It's empty. He screwed us!
- 如果我把钱带来，肯定不能活着出去 - 你错了，富小子
-lf I brought the money, I'd never get out. -Big mistake, rich boy.
我要捏断你脖子，我杀了你
I phase through your neck, I kill you.
- 我们他妈的只想要钱！ - 住手！
-We want the damn money! -Stop it!
- 给我们钱！ - 你们从来没说过要做这种事情！
-Give us the money! -You never said we'd do this!
我让你闭嘴！
I said, shut up!
住手，你会杀了他！
Stop it, you're killing him!
韦德，没时间了，我们得赶快走了！
Wade, time is almost up, we got to blow!
下次，把钱带过来！
Next time, bring the money!
惠特尼？
Whitney?
走了，菜鸟
Come on, rookie.
你怎么了，哥们？ 你在想什么呢？
What got into you, bro? What were you thinking?
- 他根本没用脑子想！ - 我不想去杀人！
-He wasn't thinking! -I didn't sign on to kill anyone.
是么，佛得曼？
Oh, is that it, Fordman?
- 你想退出这个团队？ - 我没这么说，只是…
-You trying to quit? -I'm not saying that. It's just....
莱克斯不是那种能付了钱就了事的人
Luthor doesn't seem like the kind of guy that would just pay up and then walk away.
别担心那个卢瑟，我已经吓他个半死了
Don't worry about Luthor, I put the fear of God in him!
那时我们会发大财的！
It's gonna be our biggest payday yet!
好了，好了，别这样
All right, all right, all right, that's enough.
大家都是一伙儿的
Homeboy's fine.
- 就是有点太紧张了吧？ - 是的
-Just had a case of jitters, didn't you? -Yeah.
好吧
Yeah.
- 他会把事情都搞砸了！ - 哥们，我们用那种能力已经用得精疲力尽了！
-He's gonna screw everything up! -Look at us, bro, we are burning up!
我们不能一直由自己来纹身 得要新鲜血液来保住我们的梦想
We can't just keep tatting up. We need fresh blood to keep this dream alive.
去喝点酒，冷静下
Now go get a brew and chill out.
去吧
Come on.
哥们，听着
Listen, bro.
我刚才为了保你得罪好几个弟兄了
I went out on a limb for you just now.
别让我再失望
Don't let me down again.
我不会了
I won't.
别担心那个卢瑟
And don't sweat Luthor.
他给了钱以后，肯定会消失…
As soon as he ponies up the cash, I think he's gonna disappear...
…很长时间的
...for a very long time.
走吧
Come on.
好吧，莱克斯…
All right, Lex...
…你当时准备怎么对待那帮家伙？
...what were you doing with those guys?
他们勒索我，克拉克
They were blackmailing me, Clark.
我去交易
I went there to make a drop.
你也怀疑你父亲对我的看法是对的了？
You're wondering if your father's been right about me all along, aren't you?
他们偷了个装有商业机密的电脑磁盘
They stole a computer disk that contains confidential information.
- 里面有什么？ - 并没有不合法的东西…
-What was on it? -Nothing illegal...
…但我也不想把这些东西公布于众
...but it's not something I want in the public domain.
- 所以你不想让警察介入 - 克拉克，我告诉过你我能自己处理
-That's why you didn't want cops involved. -Clark, I told you I'd handle it.
我倒想问你怎么在那？
Question is, what were you doing there?
我在跟踪惠特尼
I was following Whitney.
他和那些人混在一起，我想帮助他
He's been hanging with those guys. I wanted to help.
因为之前你没能救克罗伊吗？
Is this because of Chloe?
卡拉克，你拯救不了全世界
Clark, you can't save the world.
小心最终你的救世主情结会给你树太多敌人
All you'll end up with is a messiah complex and a lot of enemies.
我不是救了你么？也不是很糟啊
I saved you, didn't I? That turned out all right.
下一步行动呢？
What's your next move?
让他们意识到抢劫莱克斯・卢瑟是没用的
They're gonna learn that it doesn't pay to rob Lex Luthor.
惠特尼怎么办？
What about Whitney?
物以类聚
A man is measured by the quality of his friends.
如果他还和那些人在一起，就得为自己负责
If the quarterback's with them, he'll have to face the consequences.
皮特？
Pete?
你在这里干什么？我们说好在火炬报社见面
We were supposed to meet at the Torch.
是的，但是，克罗伊打电话…
Yeah, well, Chloe called...
- …我来告诉她我们做的事情… - 所以我坚持要你们来这里…
-...and I told her what we were doing.... -So I insisted you guys come here.
- 你应该好好休息 - 一直休息快让我疯了
-You should be resting. -All this resting is driving me insane.
所谓的“健康护理专家”只让我躺在床上吃果冻
These so-called "health-care professionals" just want me in bed eating Jell-O.
真是法西斯啊
Those fascists.
我也要做，不要把我排除在外，好吗？
I need to do this, okay? Don't cut me out of it, please?
好吧
Okay.
我上网做了一些研究…
So I was surfing the Net, doing some research....
你在这里怎么上网？
How'd you get online here?
皮特帮我盗了电话网
Pete hijacked the phone line for me.
有什么发现？
What have you got?
是否有可能，那些人是利用陨石纹身来加速新陈代谢？
What if these guys are using meteorite tattoos to speed up their metabolism?
我的意思是，他们体内的分子将会超高速运动
I mean, their molecules are literally moving at hyperspeed.
- 这就是他们能穿过物体的原因？ - 不可思议
-That's how they go through solid objects? -That's crazy.
可是他们做到了
Well, they're doing it.
这就像极速冲刺
It's like the ultimate rush.
但他们的身体不能承受长时间的压力
But there's no way their bodies can handle that kind of stress for long.
那你说时间长了会怎样？
What are you saying will happen?
要最快的速度，就要付出最大的代价
You take the ultimate rush, you pay the ultimate price.
妮尔？
Nell?
妮尔,是你吗？
Nell, is that you?
惠特尼
Whitney.
我有麻烦了，拉娜
I'm in trouble, Lana.
我把事情搞砸了
I messed up.
我信错了人
I trusted the wrong guys.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我让你失望了 我只是不知道要怎么办
I let you down. I just don't know what to do.
没事的，没事的
It's okay. It's okay.
他们把钱拿到手之后就会杀了莱克斯…
After they get the money, they're gonna kill Lex...
…可能也会杀了出卖他们的我
...and probably me for betraying them.
- 你做的是对的 - 我做得太少太晚了
-You did the right thing. -Yeah, too little too late.
他们现在在哪？
Where are they now?
回阁楼睡觉了
Back at the loft, sleeping it off.
- 你看到他们从莱克斯那里偷的磁盘没？ - 没有
-Did you see the disk they stole from Lex? -No.
但是一定在那里 我可以偷偷溜进去拿出来
But it's gotta be there. I can sneak in and get it.
- 太危险了，我们还是报警吧 - 不能有警察
-It's dangerous. We should call the police. -No cops.
- 我已经有太多麻烦了 - 告诉我他们在哪里
-I'm already in enough trouble. -Tell me where they are.
- 我可以在他们醒来前拿回磁盘 - 我不能让你一个人去，克拉克
-I can get in and out before they wake. -I can't let you go alone, Clark.
是我自己惹的麻烦 我要试着去解决
I got myself into this mess, I gotta try and get myself out of it.
没人，他们一定是出去找我了
Empty. They must be out looking for me.
那我们得在他们回来前找到磁盘
Well, let's find it before they come back.
这儿没有
It's not here.
继续找，一定在这儿的某个地方
Keep looking. It's gotta be here somewhere.
我找到了
I got it.
你把事情弄糟了，菜鸟
You really screwed up, rookie.
我不管你怎么找到的磁盘 但我要你还给我，现在
Look, I don't know how you found that disk, bro, but I need it back. Now.
很疼，对吗？ 感觉像有人在你肚子里乱搅一气
Hurts, doesn't it? It feels like someone's chewing up your insides.
如果时间够长 我还可以造成一些严重的损伤
I stay in long enough, I could do some serious damage.
你是下一个，兄弟
You're next, bro.
韦德，别这样
Wade, please.
继续走，菜鸟
Keep moving, rookie.
我知道在银行保险库里 你们的手臂怎么了
I know what happened to your arm in the bank vault.
是职业损伤 时间太久纹身就会失效
Occupational hazard. We waited too long.
不过不疼，我拔出来的时候 已经断了
Didn't hurt. When I pulled out, it was fused at the shoulder.
你们不能再这么做了，会死的
You can't keep doing this. You're gonna die.
如果你没有搞砸我们的退休计划 我们确实不需要再这么做
If you hadn't have screwed up our retirement plan, we wouldn't have to!
但是现在…
But now...
…你要付出代价
...you're gonna pay.
- 你怎么找到我们的？ - 拉娜打电话来…
-How'd you find us? -Lana called...
…告诉我你们的行踪 你应该先通知我
...told me what you guys were doing. You should've called me first.
-　我得去找惠特尼 -　克拉克，等一下
-I've gotta find Whitney. -Clark, wait.
我这就报警
I'm calling the police.
我本以为你懂了
I thought you understood.
这是你重获成功的机会
This was your chance to be on top again.
我本以为没有奖学金我的生活就完了 但是我错了
I thought my life was over when I lost my scholarship, but I was wrong.
不，你是对的，你是完蛋了
No. You were right, your life is over.
还记得入伙仪式吗，兄弟？ 你是那么加入我们的
Remember your initiation, bro? That's how you joined us.
你也要那样推出 时间快了，拿着遥控器
Well, that's how you're gonna leave. We're running out of time, grab the remote.
放开他
Let him go.
警察马上就到
The cops are on their way.
再好好想想，菜鸟 只有一个方法才能退出
Think again, rookie. There's only one way off this team.
别担心，我掩护你
Don't worry, I got you covered.
Yeah!
别动！
Don't move!
- 举起手来！ - 举手!
-Keep your hands up! -Keep them up!
举起手靠在汽车上!
Up against the car!
你怎么跟警察说的？
What did you tell the police?
事实
The truth.
那些人闯进了我的房子 你们俩发现了，想做英雄…
Those guys broke into my house. You two figured it out, tried to be heroes...
- …舍命来解决 - 那…？
-...and got in over your heads. -What about--?
关于穿墙的事？
Walking through walls part?
我不认为警察能处理那么多事实
I don't think the cops could handle that much truth.
可怜了你的磁盘
Sorry about your disk.
我来这不是为了磁盘，克拉克 我来是因为我的朋友有麻烦
I didn't come out here for that, Clark. I came because my friend was in trouble.
谢谢
Thanks.
记住
Just remember, boys:
你们为我保守秘密 我就为你们保守秘密
You keep my secret, and I'll keep yours.
如果不帮我保密…
And if you don't...
…你们会发现自己不是唯一有穿墙超能力的人
...you'll find out you're not the only ones who can reach through walls.
车挪开，我们要转移嫌疑人
Move this vehicle. We have to transport the suspects.
好的
Yes, sir.
- 啊，自由的味道 - 你只是住进了医院，不是监狱
-Ah, the sweet smell of freedom. -You were in the hospital, not Alcatraz.
你呆一个星期也会觉得自己像个囚犯
You spend a week in there and you'd feel like a prisoner too. Come on.
食物乏味，九点熄灯，还没电视
Bad food, lights out by nine and no cable?
我觉得这情况需要被曝光
I'm thinking about doing an expose.
- 顺便问问，惠特尼怎么样？ - 他得慢慢来想开
-How's Whitney, by the way? -He's taking it one day at a time.
好的，那么，再见了
Good. All right, well, bye.
- 噢，抱歉 - 克罗伊，你去哪？
-Oh, sorry. -Chloe, where are you going?
我去跟警察做些核实
I'm gonna do some checking with the police.
阁楼里没有找到纹身液
None of the tattoo ink was found at the loft...
…斯科特和德瑞克也没有透露任何东西，所以…
...and Scott and Derek aren't saying anything to anyone, so....
可能有包庇隐瞒
I smell a cover-up.
克罗伊？
Chloe?
很高兴真正的你又回来了
It's good to have you back.
谢谢
Thanks.
他来早了
He's early.
碰碰运气吧
Okay, here goes nothing.
这是个很好的计划
It's a good plan.
谢谢你的帮助，祝我好运吧
Thanks for all your help. Wish me luck.
你不需要运气也能成功
You don't need it.
谢谢你能来
Thanks for coming.
接到电话我很惊讶
I was surprised by your call.
上次见面之后 我以为你不会再找我了
After our last meeting, I didn't think I'd hear from you again.
这次我有备而来
This time I came prepared.
这是什么？
What's this?
我的商业计划书
My business proposal.
小城镇都正在复兴他们的商业区
Small towns across the country have revived their downtowns...
…将它们恢复成以前的社会中心 他们没有…
...returning them to the social centers they once were. They didn't do this...
…靠建造千篇一律的商场或停车场
...by building cookie-cutter malls or parking garages.
而是重新运作已有建筑…
They did it by restoring the great buildings that were already there...
……将它们改造成咖啡馆，书店，餐馆
...turning them into cafes, bookstores, restaurants.
你想让这房子变成咖啡馆或者书店？
You want to turn the Talon into a cafe/bookstore?
它也可以改造成本地乐队或者艺术电影的聚集地
It could also be a venue for local bands and arthouse movies.
在计划书的十二页写着 这栋建筑可以注册为…
I found out you can register the building...
…历史遗迹，这样还可以少收税
...as a historic landmark, which gives you certain tax benefits.
不过千万别让我解释详细原因
Just don't ask me to explain them.
谁来负责这个？
Who's gonna manage it?
妮尔说她会感兴趣的
Nell said she'd be interested.
我可以在放学后和她一起培训 争取暑假内就开张营业
And I can train with her after school, and try running it myself in the summers.
你怎么想到这个的？
How'd you come up with this?
克拉克给了一些建议 他告诉我你喜欢给别人挑战
Something Clark said. He told me you like to challenge people.
那么，显然你准备接受挑战了
Well, you've definitely risen to the challenge.
成交了？
So it's a deal?
我需要再检查下细节，不过…
I need to look over everything but, yeah...
- …成交了 - 真的吗？
-...it's a deal. -Really?
真的
Really.
我觉得这会是一段有趣合作的开始
I think this could be the start of a very interesting partnership.